plug.game 2018-12-21

# PLUG : mobile game community

### Privacy Policy

PLUG Privacy Policy

Effective Date: May 17, 2017

**1\. Collected personal information**

The Company supports various social login to support convenient registration and use of service, and as such processes personal information as below during the process. However, supported social login types and methods may vary by country.  
1\. NAVER account registration: account, public profile information (name, profile picture, age range, gender), and nickname  
2\. Facebook account registration: account, public profile information (name, profile picture, age range, gender), nickname, and email address  
3\. Twitter, Google, LINE, Wechat, and Weibo account registration: account, profile picture, and nickname  
4\. Email account registration: Email address, password, and nickname 

While using the service information such as IP address, service use history, violation history, and device information may be automatically collected.  
In addition, while using the service and application or executing the SDK, IP address, cookie, visit date, service use history, violation history, device information, and location information may be collected, and during customer service reception and processing email address may be collected. 

**2\. Method of collecting personal information**

The Company collects personal information directly from the user for account registration and use of service. Also while the user logs in to the service or uses the service information such as cookie and IP address may be automatically generated and collected.

**3\. Collecting personal information and purpose**

The Company utilizes personal information in order to provide website and mobile services such as providing contents, customized services, identification, friend search, alarm, and invites.  
Personal information is also used for member management purposes such as to provide service for registered members, identify users, restrict users violating PLUG Terms of Service, restrict and limit behaviors that disrupt proper service operation and unauthorized service use, confirm registration, limit registration and registration count, maintain history in case of disputes, customer care, handling complaints, and to confirm account deletion.  
In addition personal information may be utilized for various marketing and advertisement purposes such as new service development, service provision and advertisement according to statistical characteristics, confirm validity of service, provide event information and participation chances, confirm access frequency, and statistical analysis of service use by members. 

**4\. Sharing and providing personal information**

The Company will use the personal information of users only within the limits notified in "3. Collecting personal information and purpose ", and personal information will not be used outside of these boundaries and will not be exposed to third parties without prior consent of the user. However, the Company may be required to provide personal information due to legal obligations.

**5\. Co-handling of personal information**

The Company commissions part of personal information as below for convenience of the user and provision of service. Commission period is until account is deleted or until the commission contract is terminated.  
1\. NAVER Business Platform©: system operation necessary for service provision  
2\. NHN Technology Services©: service development and testing  
3\. NNIT Service©: infrastructure operation 

**6\. User rights and execution**

User or legal representatives may view or edit the registered personal information of themselves or their children under 14 years of age, and if not agreeing to the Company’s personal information processing, may refuse consent or request account deletion. In detail, to directly view, edit, or delete information, click ‘My profile’ (or ‘Account management’ and such) to view or edit personal information, or click “Delete account” to delete the account (withdraw consent). If the user requests correction of incorrect personal information, the personal information will not be provided until the information is corrected. In addition, if the personal information is already provided to third parties, the correction will be notified and corrected to the third party as soon as possible. 

**7\. Installation/operation of automatic personal information collecting device and rejection**

1\. Company’s purpose of using cookie information

Cookie information is used in order to determine the user’s purpose for using and visiting the PLUG service to provide customized and optimized information with advertisements to the user.

2\. Installment/operation of cookie information and refusal

The user has the right to decide on cookie installation. As such the user may set web browser settings to allow all cookies, ask for permission when saving cookies, or refuse to save all cookies. However, if refusing to save cookies, then there may be some inconveniences when using certain PLUG services that require login.  
The user may change the web browser settings to allow all cookies, ask for permission when saving cookies, or refuse all cookies.

**8\. Personal information retention and use period**

The user’s personal information is destroyed without delay when the collection purpose is satisfied or when the user deletes the account. However, nicknames saved with posts may be retained along with the post without separate deletion.  
In addition personal information of users who violated the Terms of Service and policies may be retained for a certain amount of time before being destroyed according to internal policies. And if the Company is obliged to retain personal information for a certain amount of time due to legal obligations, the Company will preserve personal information for that amount of time.

**9\. Disposal method and process of personal information**

Personal information printed on paper will be shredded or burned for disposal, and personal information saved as in electronic data file format will be deleted using technical methods that prevent data recovery.

**10\. Technical/administrative protection of personal information**

While handling personal information of users, the Company takes the following technical/administrative measures to ensure the safety of personal information to prevent loss, theft, leak, modification, or damage.

1\. Password encryption

Account passwords are saved and managed after encryption and therefor only the account owner knows the password, and as such viewing and changing personal information can only be done by the account owner with the account password.

2\. Measures against hacking

The Company takes all possible measures to prevent leakage or damage of personal information of users by hacking or computer viruses. Personal information data is continuously backed up in case of damage, and the latest antivirus software is used to prevent leakage or damage of personal information of users, and network encryption is used to safely transmit personal information.  
Unauthorized external access is restricted using an intrusion prevention system, and all possible technical measures are taken to ensure system safety and security.

3\. Education and minimal personnel for handling

The Company limits personnel handling personal information to the manager, and a separate password is authorized and regularly updated for this purpose. The manager is continuously trained to prioritize Privacy Policy of PLUG.

4\. Dedicated department for personal information security

A separate internal department is dedicated for personal information security to review PLUG Privacy Policy procedures and compliance of managers so that problems are corrected immediately when found. However, the Company is not responsible for any problems that occur due to the negligence of the user or internet problems causing exposure of user names, passwords, and other personal information.

**11\. Personal information protection division contact information**

The user may report all problems and complaints related to personal information to the Privacy&Security team. The Company will review and respond to all reports as soon as possible.  
\- Privacy&Security email address: [cafeplugsupport@naver.com](mailto:cafeplugsupport@naver.com)

**12\. Applicable principles and range**

This Privacy Policy does not apply to externally linked pages or personal information processing of other businesses.

**13\. Personal information handling changes**

When parts of this Privacy Policy is added, deleted, or edited the information will be notified on the website’s ‘Notification’ or through email at least 7 days in advance. However, if there is a change to personal information collection, use purpose, provision, and other important changes regarding the rights of users, such information will be notified or informed at least 30 days in advance.

Announced Date: February 9, 2017  
Effective Date: May 17, 2017
